ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Additional Records
1970-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4115
18.5 cubic feet
18.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
7989297
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 30, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /4063: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4115 AV: ILR School Extension Division Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension Division.
7989297
- Retention & Expansion (Box 1)
  - Cornell University - Rochester College Extension Program, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller College - SUNY Albany, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- NFLD Fieldwork Notes (Box 2)
  - Newfoundland Maps and Fieldwork Notes, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes several topographic maps
  - Newfoundland Fieldwork, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Includes news clippings
  - Notes for Ramea Project, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ramea Project Notes, Maps, and Letters, 1965-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes topographic maps of Ramea and Newfoundland and hand-drawn maps of Ramea businesses and landmarks
  - Making a Living - Planters, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Includes a topographic map
  - Making a Living - Salmon Fishing (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Gear (Banking Schooners), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gear (West Shore Schooners) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Environment - Perceived (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Environment - Affective Environment (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Making a Living - Alternative Employment (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interaction - Neighborhood (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Interaction - Kinship (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Gear (Skiffs) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Quiz #6 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Gear (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Fieldwork (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Note for Newfoundland Project, Untyped, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Setting (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Environment - Assorted (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chapter V (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Burgeo's Fight for Heart and Mind, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    July 31, 1971; article in The Global Magazine
  - Newfoundland Salmon Fisheries Regulations, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Mostly English/French material
  - Newfoundland - Nation and Province, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    From The Canadian Forum, March 1974
  - Message from the Trawlermen, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hakluyt's Voyages Volume VIII (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Environment - Climate (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Burgeo: Second Time Around, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    From the Union Forum, August 1971
  - Project Table of Contents (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Union Surveys (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Notes on Ramea Attitudes toward Unions, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Source Notecards (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Newfoundland Census Records and Miscellany, 1836-1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - South Coast Economy (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - References - Ramea 1976, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Preface (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Project Notes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Handlining - Gear, Vessels, Shoal Water, Deep Water (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Trawl Territoriality (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Gear (conclusion) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Making a Living - Structures and Values (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Interaction - Community (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Info yet to get - Ramea Project 1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Making a Living - Draggers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Newfoundland Project - Questionnaires and Outline (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Eastern Canadian Seafarers Project, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Notes for a Documentary on the South Coast (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Appendix (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Merchant Reactions, 1951-1981 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Newman, Hunt and Company Records - Index and Introduction (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Attitudes toward Unionization by Occupation and Age (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Making a Living - Fishing (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Extension Attic (Box 3)
  - The Neighborworks Directory, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Center for Manufacturing Enterprise 5/8/93 Conference, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    May 8, 1993; includes a map of Cornell University
  - The Tennessee Business Retention and Expansion Program, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes a map of Nashville
  - The Ohio Business Retention and Expansion Program, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Forum October 18-19, 1991, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Includes new clippings; includes transparencies
  - Economic Initiatives and Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Western New York Wood Industry, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Upstate New York Economic Development Partnership (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Economic Development - Syracuse, Rochester, and Ithaca, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Developing Communication Skills, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Development and Competitiveness, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Extension Programs and Resources, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Includes a map of Cornell University
  - Capital District Regional Planning Commission, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Social Trends and Outlook Conference (STOC) Presentation and Miscellany, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    May 4-5, 1993
  - Ohio Business Retention and Expansion Program Handbook, 1986-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Includes news clippings as part of the handbook
  - Public Choice, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Performance Appraisal and Interpersonal Communication, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Volunteer Motivation and Retention, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Includes transparencies
  - Cost Avoidance, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grantsmanship Seminar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grantsmanship Workshop (Box 3, Folder 22)
- CCFL Grad Info (Box 4)
  - Instructor Letter of Agreement - Graduate Credits, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Career Development - Ithaca, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Independent Study - CCFL (College Center for the Finger Lakes) Winter 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Human Resource Studies Credit - R. House (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hispanic Labor Studies Credit, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CCFL Spring 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CCFL Fall 1986 - Graduate ILR 662 and 655 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Independent Study CCFL Graduate 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CCFL Graduate Certificate 1986 - Graduation (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - CCFL 1986 Graduate, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CCFL Winter 1986 Graduate, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CCFL Fall 1985, 1976-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CCFL Graduate Certificate 1985 - Graduation (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CCFL Spring 1985 Graduate ILR 501 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CCFL Spring 1985 Graduate ILR 560 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - CCFL Winter 1985 Graduate ILR 669, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - CCFL Winter 1985 Graduate ILR 667, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - CCFL Fall 1984 Graduate ILR 728, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - CCFL Fall 1984 Graduate ILR 681 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - CCFL Spring 1984 Graduate ILR 500, 1971-1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - CCFL Winter 1984 Graduate ILR 661, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - CCFL Fall 1983 Graduate ILR 560 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - CCFL Winter 1983 Graduate ILR 728, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    One letter includes an attached fee of $2 cash
  - CCFL Summer 1983 Graduate ILR 684 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - CCFL General Information, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - CCFL Management Meeting for Career Development Studies 5/17/84, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Luncheon meeting was held May 17, 1984
  - Albany Spring 1987 Course Number 120 681 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Albany Fall 1986 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Albany Fall 1985 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Albany Winter 1985 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Albany Fall 1984 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Albany Spring 1984 Graduate ILR 602 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Hofstra Fall 1984 Graduate, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ithaca Fall 1986 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Ithaca Winter 1986 Graduate ILR 560, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Ithaca Fall 1985 Graduate (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Ithaca Spring 1985 Graduate, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - CCFL Miscellaneous Correspondence - Graduate and Career Development Information, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Rochester Spring 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Rochester Fall 1987, 1968-1987 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Rochester Spring 1987 Graduate, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Extension Attic (Box 5)
  - Social Trends and Outlook Conference (STOC), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Tioga County, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins County, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Transaction Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Work Plan, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Seneca County, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Research Task Groups, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rockland County, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Conference, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Steering Committee (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Services Sector Questionnaire, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Essential Business Activities Questionnaire (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Regulations, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Renesselaer County, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Paper, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Community and Rural Development, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Community Centered Planning, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Program Resource Guide, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Presentation Materials for the Rural Resources Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Participatory Action Research (PAR), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Schuyler Draft, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - New Paltz Research, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Networking Project, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Networks, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Building Industrial Competitiveness in Rural Areas, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - I/O (Input/Output) IMPLAN Model (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rural Business Incubators, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Economic Vitality Initiative, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kellogg, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - LGP (Local Government Program) Brochure (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Economic Development Administration (EDA) Site Visit - Appraisal of the Cornell Local Government Program, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Evaluation, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fiscal Impact (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Flowchart (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Guidebook, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Brochure, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Includes a transparency
  - Cayuga County, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Center for Manufacturing Enterprise, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Considering a Local R and E Program (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Cost Estimates, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Economic Profile, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Defense Technology Conversion Reinvestment and Transition Assistance (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Economic Development Digest, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    April 1993
  - Agreements (Retention and Expansion Programs), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Application Form - Retention and Expansion Programs, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - The Aspen Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Schuyler County Transparencies (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Entirely transparencies
  - Community Experience with Government Agencies, Local Services, and Businesses (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Retention and Expansion Analysis for Communities in Transition (REACT), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Includes three 5 1/4 Floppy Disks
  - Community Resources - Minnesota Extension Service, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Computer Software User's Guides, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - New York 34th District Economic Development Study, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    Includes a 3 1/2 Floppy Disk
  - Schuyler County Business Retention and Expansion Program Data and Overview, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous Business Retention and Expansion Programs, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Robert Rich Correspondence and Cattaraugus County Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - The Business Center, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Schuyler County Trade and Outlook Transparencies (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence - Putnam, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Putnam County Business Retention and Expansion Program Application for Funds and Economic Overview, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Statewide Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Cattaraugus County Proposal for Economic Development Assistance Grant, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Consultant Selection, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence - Cost Estimates, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Data Base, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    Folder appears to be missing some kind of Floppy Disk
  - Partnership, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Services Sector - Survey Research Facility (SRF), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Mercer Management Consulting, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Unsorted Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Alcohol Papers (Box 6)
  - Alcohol and Drug Intervention in the Workplace Transparencies (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Includes mostly transparencies
  - Peer/Member Assistance, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Employee Assistance Programs (EAP), 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Program on Alcoholism and Occupational Health (PAOH) Video Collection, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Women and Addictions, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University Reports on Alcohol and Drug Addictions in the Workplace (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Federal and State Reports, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Alcohol and Drug Studies, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - EAP Policy Statement, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Employee Assistance Certification Commission/Employee Assistance Professionals Association (EACC/EAPA), 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Professional Development Hours (PDH) Certificates to be processed, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - EAP Training Materials I, 1976-1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - EAP Training Materials II, 1973-1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Some material with English/French/German abstracts
  - Therapy Studies, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - EAP Miscellany, 1982-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - New York Federation of Alcoholism Counselors (NYFAC) - Credentialed Alcoholism Counselor (CAC) Hours, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Level I - December 1989 Field Test, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Level I Seminar entitled "Work Organizations and Troubled Employees"
  - Level I Field Test January 23-24 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Media/AV, 1980-1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Association for Children of Alcoholics (ACOA)/Co-Dependents (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Foundations Research, 1973-1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Reintegration/Return to Work, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Other Addictions - Gambling and Eating Disorders, 1981-1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - AIDS and EAPs, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - AIDS, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Systems Automation, 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    This folder was moved from Box 3 to Box 6 due to lack of space; includes transparencies
  - Social Trends, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Listening, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    This folder was moved from Box 3 to Box 6 due to lack of space
  - Farewell to Bob Rich, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Extension Attic (Box 7)
  - Telecommunications and the Internet for Local Development, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Participatory Action Research (PAR), 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Includes a poster; includes news clippings as part of a bound case study
  - Action Learning, Action Research, and Process Management Association, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hy-Rosenblum Administration Center (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Includes a map
  - Cornell Local Government Program and Course Development, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mario Einaudi Center for International Studies, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Public Participation Practitioners (IAP3), 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ira Harkavy and the University of Pennsylvania, 1989-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Southern Tier New York, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - O'Reilly Publishing and Software Catalog, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Unsorted Miscellany, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Worker Ownership Resource Center (WORC), 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Business Retention and Expansion, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Telecommunications Initiatives, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Includes new clippings; includes a map of Corning
  - Action Research, 1984-1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Agriculture and Rural Development, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Telecommunications Consortium, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Telecommunications and New York's Local Governments, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Sustainability, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - The Internet and Computers Miscellany, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Includes a 3 1/ 2 Floppy Disk; includes news casters
  - Info Tech Report, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Collaborative Action Research, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Boarder Rights Coalition - Participatory Action Research, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Includes some English/Spanish material
  - Cornell Administration, Faculty, and Miscellany, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Polaroid, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Healthcare, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Includes a map of a hospital campus in Elmira
  - In Focus, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Unsorted Material, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Retention & Expansion (Box 8)
  - Cattaraugus County Business Retention and Expansion Program Questionnaire I, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cattaraugus County Business Retention and Expansion Program Questionnaire II, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Cattaraugus County Business Retention and Expansion Program Questionnaire III, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus county Business Retention and Expansion Program Questionnaire IV, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Schuyler County Business Retention and Expansion Survey 1992 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Includes two 3 1/2 Floppy Disks
  - Staff Meetings 1993 (Cornell University Local Government Program) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Evaluating New York State Counties, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Economic Revitalization and Development, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Revised Tables mad Questionnaire - Business Retention and Expansion - Winter 1991/1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Post-Cattaraugus Survey Revision (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Cattaraugus County Employment Statistics, 1955-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Cattaraugus County Retention and Expansion Survey, 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Includes a map of Olean, Allegany, and Portville and the area around those towns
  - Schuyler County Retention and Expansion, 1983-1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Cattaraugus County - Service Sector Retention and Expansion, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Cattaraugus County - Retention and Expansion Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ohio State Retention and Expansion - Original Program, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Contains a 5 inch Floppy Disk containing the original data from a State University of Ohio report
  - Cattaraugus Retention and Expansion - Carla's Really Important Stuff (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cattaraugus Retention and Expansion - Tables (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Contains a blank copy of the Cattaraugus County Business Retention and Expansion Program survey with revision markings - and nothing else
- Retention & Expansion (Box 9)
  - Retention and Expansion Readings, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Economic Development - Ohio State Retention and Expansion Program, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cattaraugus County Business Retention and Expansion Program 1991 Interim Report - Multiple Copies (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Cooperative Extension, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Computer Program Printouts, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Robert Rich Correspondence, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Smithers (Box 10)
  - Employee Assistance Education and Research Program - Folder 1, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Includes some Spanish language material
  - Employee Assistance Education and Research Program - Folder 2, 1968-1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Marketing of Employee Assistance Programs (EAPs) - Session 1-3, Spring 1989, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Packet includes previous academic studies
  - Book Review by William Sonnenstuhl on Cooper and Smith - ASQ, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Work reviewed is "Job Stress and Blue Collar Work"
  - Clinical Issues - Session 3-12, 1989 Folder 1, 1963-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Training material includes previous academic research
  - Clinical Issues - Session 3-12, 1989 Folder 2, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Employee Assistance Education and Research Program (EAERP) - Labor History - Buffalo, New York, 1978-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - EAERP Interviews (A-L) - Instructors (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Thirteen 5 inch Floppy Disks
  - EAERP Interviews (M-Z) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Fourteen 5 inch Floppy Disks
  - EAERP Interviews (AA-MM) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Disks (NN-) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    eight 5 inch Floppy Disks
- Extension Attic (Box 11)
  - Dissertation - Crosshanded: Work Organization and Values in a Newfoundland Fishery, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Improving the Efficiency of Maritime Personnel 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Consultation - National Institute of Mental Health, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Human Error in Maritime Casualty and Near Casualty, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The American Seafarer Series - Deep Sea Officers Studies, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The National Shipbuilding Research Program (NSRP) - 1985 Ship Production Symposium (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Seagoing Workforce, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Human Error in the Merchant Marine, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Human Element in Ship Operations - Maine Maritime Academy, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Manning of Vessels, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Exxon Shipping Company - Fleet Management Conference, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Conference Notes, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Effect of Smaller Crews on Maritime Safety, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Effective Manning at American President Lines, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Size of Crews, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Michael Gaffney - Maritime Transportation Research Board, 1977-1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Includes some English/French material
- Extension Attic (Box 12)
  - Ulster County Business Retention and Expansion Needs Assessment, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ulster County Business Retention and Expansion Needs Assessment Interviewer's Manual and other Materials, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ulster County Survey - Bob Rich and Bob Kelchner, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ulster Survey Documents Correspondence, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Questionnaire Development, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Retention and Expansion (R and E) Conceptual Model, 1986-1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Infinite Disk - Hierarchical Storage Management for the PC, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Item is a book
  - Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Item is a book; published in 1974, signed in 1976
  - Basic Marketing, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)